<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cluster Deployment on Apache HoraeDB</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/</link><description>Recent content in Cluster Deployment on Apache HoraeDB</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NoMeta</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/no_meta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/no_meta/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Note: This feature is for testing use only, not recommended for production use, related features may change in the future.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This guide shows how to deploy a HoraeDB cluster without HoraeMeta, but with static, rule-based routing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The crucial point here is that HoraeDB server provides configurable routing function on table name so what we need is just a valid config containing routing rules which will be shipped to every HoraeDB instance in the cluster.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>WithMeta</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/with_meta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/cluster_deployment/with_meta/</guid><description>&lt;p>This guide shows how to deploy a HoraeDB cluster with HoraeMeta. And with the HoraeMeta, the whole HoraeDB cluster will feature: high availability, load balancing and horizontal scalability if the underlying storage used by HoraeDB is separated service.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="deploy-horaemeta">Deploy HoraeMeta&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="introduce">Introduce&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>HoraeMeta is one of the core services of HoraeDB distributed mode, it is used to manage and schedule the HoraeDB cluster. By the way, the high availability of HoraeMeta is ensured by embedding &lt;a href="https://github.com/etcd-io/etcd">ETCD&lt;/a>. Also, the ETCD service is provided for HoraeDB servers to manage the distributed shard locks.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>