<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SQL Syntax on Apache HoraeDB</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/</link><description>Recent content in SQL Syntax on Apache HoraeDB</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Identifier</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/identifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/identifier/</guid><description>Identifier in HoraeDB can be used as table name, column name etc. It cannot be preserved keywords or start with number and punctuation symbols. HoraeDB allows to quote identifiers with back quotes (`). In this case it can be any string like 00_table or select.</description></item><item><title>Utility Statements</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/utility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/utility/</guid><description>There are serval utilities SQL in HoraeDB that can help in table manipulation or query inspection.
SHOW CREATE TABLE SHOW CREATE TABLE table_name; SHOW CREATE TABLE returns a CREATE TABLE DDL that will create a same table with the given one. Including columns, table engine and options. The schema and options shows in CREATE TABLE will based on the current version of the table. An example:
-- create one table CREATE TABLE `t` (a bigint, b int default 3, c string default &amp;#39;x&amp;#39;, d smallint null, t timestamp NOT NULL, TIMESTAMP KEY(t)) ENGINE = Analytic; -- Result: affected_rows: 0 -- show how one table should be created.</description></item><item><title>Options</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/engine_options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/engine_options/</guid><description>Options below can be used when create table for analytic engine
enable_ttl, bool. When enable TTL on a table, rows older than ttl will be deleted and can&amp;rsquo;t be querid, default true
ttl, duration, lifetime of a row, only used when enable_ttl is true. default 7d.
storage_format, string. The underlying column&amp;rsquo;s format. Availiable values:
columnar, default hybrid, Note: This feature is still in development, and it may change in the future.</description></item><item><title>Scalar Functions</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/scalar_functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/scalar_functions/</guid><description>HoraeDB SQL is implemented with DataFusion, Here is the list of scalar functions. See more detail, Refer to Datafusion
Math Functions Function Description abs(x) absolute value acos(x) inverse cosine asin(x) inverse sine atan(x) inverse tangent atan2(y, x) inverse tangent of y / x ceil(x) nearest integer greater than or equal to argument cos(x) cosine exp(x) exponential floor(x) nearest integer less than or equal to argument ln(x) natural logarithm log10(x) base 10 logarithm log2(x) base 2 logarithm power(base, exponent) base raised to the power of exponent round(x) round to nearest integer signum(x) sign of the argument (-1, 0, +1) sin(x) sine sqrt(x) square root tan(x) tangent trunc(x) truncate toward zero Conditional Functions Function Description coalesce Returns the first of its arguments that is not null.</description></item><item><title>Aggregate Functions</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/aggregate_functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sql/aggregate_functions/</guid><description>HoraeDB SQL is implemented with DataFusion, Here is the list of aggregate functions. See more detail, Refer to Datafusion
General Function Description min Returns the minimum value in a numerical column max Returns the maximum value in a numerical column count Returns the number of rows avg Returns the average of a numerical column sum Sums a numerical column array_agg Puts values into an array Statistical Function Description var / var_samp Returns the variance of a given column var_pop Returns the population variance of a given column stddev / stddev_samp Returns the standard deviation of a given column stddev_pop Returns the population standard deviation of a given column covar / covar_samp Returns the covariance of a given column covar_pop Returns the population covariance of a given column corr Returns the correlation coefficient of a given column Approximate Function Description approx_distinct Returns the approximate number (HyperLogLog) of distinct input values approx_median Returns the approximate median of input values.</description></item></channel></rss>