<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SDK on Apache HoraeDB</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/</link><description>Recent content in SDK on Apache HoraeDB</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Go</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/go/</guid><description>Installation go get github.com/apache/incubator-horaedb-client-go You can get latest version here.
How To Use Init HoraeDB Client client, err := horaedb.NewClient(endpoint, horaedb.Direct, horaedb.WithDefaultDatabase(&amp;#34;public&amp;#34;), ) option name description defaultDatabase using database, database can be overwritten by ReqContext in single Write or SQLRequest RPCMaxRecvMsgSize configration for grpc MaxCallRecvMsgSize, default 1024 _ 1024 _ 1024 RouteMaxCacheSize If the maximum number of router cache size, router client whill evict oldest if exceeded, default is 10000 Notice:</description></item><item><title>Java</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/java/</guid><description>Introduction HoraeDB Client is a high-performance Java client for HoraeDB.
Requirements Java 8 or later is required for compilation Dependency &amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt; &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;io.ceresdb&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;ceresdb-all&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;${CERESDB.VERSION}&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dependency&amp;gt; You can get latest version here.
Init HoraeDB Client final CeresDBOptions opts = CeresDBOptions.newBuilder(&amp;#34;127.0.0.1&amp;#34;, 8831, DIRECT) // CeresDB default grpc port 8831，use DIRECT RouteMode .database(&amp;#34;public&amp;#34;) // use database for client, can be overridden by the RequestContext in request // maximum retry times when write fails // (only some error codes will be retried, such as the routing table failure) .</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/python/</guid><description>Introduction horaedb-client is the python client for HoraeDB.
Thanks to PyO3, the python client is actually a wrapper on the rust client.
The guide will give a basic introduction to the python client by example.
Requirements Python &amp;gt;= 3.7 Installation pip install ceresdb-client You can get latest version here.
Init HoraeDB Client The client initialization comes first, here is a code snippet:
import asyncio import datetime from ceresdb_client import Builder, RpcContext, PointBuilder, ValueBuilder, WriteRequest, SqlQueryRequest, Mode, RpcConfig rpc_config = RpcConfig() rpc_config = RpcConfig() rpc_config.</description></item><item><title>Rust</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/rust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/user-guide/sdk/rust/</guid><description>Install cargo add ceresdb-client You can get latest version here.
Init Client At first, we need to init the client.
New builder for the client, and you must set endpoint and mode: endpoint is a string which is usually like &amp;ldquo;ip/domain_name:port&amp;rdquo;. mode is used to define the way to access horaedb server, detail about mode. let mut builder = Builder::new(&amp;#34;ip/domain_name:port&amp;#34;, Mode::Direct/Mode::Proxy); New and set rpc_config, it can be defined on demand or just use the default value, detail about rpc config: let rpc_config = RpcConfig { thread_num: Some(1), default_write_timeout: Duration::from_millis(1000), .</description></item></channel></rss>