<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Apache HoraeDB</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Apache HoraeDB</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/getting-started/</guid><description>&lt;p>This page shows you how to get started with HoraeDB quickly. You&amp;rsquo;ll start a standalone HoraeDB server, and then insert and read some sample data using SQL.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="start-server">Start server&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/apache/incubator-horaedb/pkgs/container/horaedb-server">HoraeDB docker image&lt;/a> is the easiest way to get started, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed Docker, go &lt;a href="https://www.docker.com/products/docker-desktop/">there&lt;/a> to install it first.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Note: please choose tag version &amp;gt;= v1.0.0, others are mainly for testing.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>You can use command below to start a standalone server&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contribution Guidelines</title><link>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/contribution-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://horaedb.apache.org/docs/contribution-guidelines/</guid><description>&lt;p>Thank you for thinking of contributing! We very much welcome contributions from the community.
To make the process easier and more valuable for everyone involved we have a few rules and guidelines to follow.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="submitting-issues-and-feature-requests">Submitting Issues and Feature Requests&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before you file an &lt;a href="https://github.com/apache/horaedb/issues/new">issue&lt;/a>, please search existing issues in case the same or similar issues have already been filed.
If you find an existing open ticket covering your issue then please avoid adding &amp;ldquo;ðŸ‘&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;me too&amp;rdquo; comments; GitHub notifications can cause a lot of noise for the project maintainers who triage the back-log.
However, if you have a new piece of information for an existing ticket, and you think it may help the investigation or resolution, then please do add it as a comment!
You can signal to the team that you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing an existing issue with one of GitHub&amp;rsquo;s emoji reactions (these are a good way to add &amp;ldquo;weight&amp;rdquo; to an issue from a prioritisation perspective).&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>